(upbeat music)
♪ Well, tell me do you
think it'd be all right ♪
♪ If I could just
crash here tonight ♪
♪ You can see I'm in
no shape for driving ♪
♪ And anyway, I've
got no place to go ♪
♪ And you know it
might not be that bad ♪
♪ You were the
best I'd ever had ♪
♪ If I hadn't blown the
whole thing years ago ♪
♪ I might not be alone ♪
♪ Tomorrow we can drive
around this town ♪
♪ And let the cops
chase us around ♪
♪ The past is gone,
but something might be found ♪
♪ To take its place ♪
♪ Hey jealousy ♪
♪ And you can trust
me not to think ♪
♪ And not to sleep around ♪
♪ And if you don't
expect too much from me ♪
♪ You might not be let down ♪
♪ 'Cause all I really
want is to be with you ♪
♪ Feeling like I matter too ♪
♪ If I hadn't blown the
whole thing years ago ♪
♪ I might be here with you ♪
♪ Tomorrow we can drive
around this town ♪
♪ And let the cops
chase us around ♪
♪ The past is gone,
but something might be found ♪
♪ To take its place ♪
♪ Hey jealousy ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Tomorrow we can drive
around this town ♪
♪ And let the cops
chase us around ♪
♪ The past is gone,
but something might be found ♪
♪ To take its place ♪
♪ Hey jealousy ♪
♪ Well, tell me,
do you think it'd be all right ♪
♪ If I could just
crash here tonight ♪
♪ You can see I'm in
no shape for driving ♪
♪ And anyway,
I've got no place to go ♪
♪ And you know it
might not be that bad ♪
♪ You were the
best I'd ever had ♪
♪ If I hadn't blown the
whole thing years ago ♪
♪ I might not be alone ♪
♪ Tomorrow we can drive
around this town ♪
♪ And let the cops
chase us around ♪
♪ The past is gone,
but something might be found ♪
♪ To take its place ♪
♪ Hey jealousy ♪
♪ She took my heart ♪
♪ Well, there's only one
thing I couldn't start ♪
♪♪♪